(Raj:)It's interesting your father
didn't help around the house
(Raj:)and Howard doesn't help, either,
(Raj:)so... in a way,
(Raj:)Howard's not only
like your father,
(Raj:)but he's also like the child
that you're afraid to have.
(Howard:)Why are you still here?
(Raj:)Fine, I'll leave.
(Raj:)But it sounds like
somebody needs a fresh diaper.
(Bernadette:)All right...
(Howard:)I admit...
that I don't help out a lot.
(chuckles softly)
And I need to work on that.
(Howard:)But...
(sighs) if we had a kid,
(Howard:)it would be different.
(Bernadette:)Why?
Because...
(Howard:)when my dad left,
(Howard:)I promised myself that...
(Howard:)if I ever had a chance
to be a father...
(Howard:)I'd always be there.
(Bernadette:)Okay, I'll think about it.
(Howard:)And this an actual
“I'll think about it,”